Now that we have a clean palette, we're going to move on to the eyebrows.
I'm going to go ahead and fill in Amy's eyebrows, you can use eyebrow liner, in this case I'm going to use powder.
A lot of makeup artists that I know, use powder as well instead of the actual liner, it just gives it a softer, more subtle look than the harshness of a liner.
So, I'm going to pick out the color that I think is closest to her eyebrow and I'm going to use an angled brush like this, and this is my favorite brush for filling in the eyebrows, I use it on myself, I use it on all of my clients, this brush, you can get this brush pretty much at every makeup counter.
I'm not sure if you can get it at drugstores, but I know you can get it at every makeup counter, you can get it at you can get it at any beauty supply store.
So, you're just going to take a little of that eye shadow is what I'm using.
And another cool little trick is so that I don't lift makeup off of her skin, I'm going to apply the puff onto her cheek and rest my hand here while I apply the eye shadow onto her eyebrow or fill in her eyebrows.
So, now I'm just taking this angled brush and I'm stroking upwards, filling in her eyebrows where it's needed and then I'll come back for more product once I run out and you want to just again slough off some of the excess eye shadow that you may have.
See how it's filling in really nicely?
The difference between the two eyebrows (Can I have your chin over here?)?
Same thing, I put the puff down, so I don't lift off of her skin on yourself you probably wouldn't do this, but if you're playing with somebody else?s eyebrows and filling in somebody else?s eyebrows if you, it's a good little trick so that you don't lift off any of the foundation.
That's filling in eyebrows!